Coming up, what has Joe and Murr jumping for joy?
Why is Sal all smiles?
And why is tonight's big loser throwing temper tantrum?
Prepare for something amazing.
Q
Murr
Sal
Joe
Today, we are teaming up at America's sub shop, Blimpie!
While helping customers get their sandwich on
We'll have to do and say what the other guys tell us.
If you refuse anything, you lose!
Carve up, fellas!  It's go time!
Joe, stab Murray in his throat.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't want to lose.
You refuse -- refuse that.
I can't lose.
Welcome to Blimpie. How are you?
Hey, how's it going?
Since it's a mother-daughter combo, we're gonna go easy on you guys.
Just bump into each other a lot.
I'm gonna get the Blimpie best.
—Half-inch?  —Yes.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
What's on the French Dip?
French Dip?
We usually do Swiss... with the roast beef.
It's on the Ciabatta bread... I'm sorry.
Ciabatta bread, typically.
The daughter's starting to pick up on it.
Joe, just yell out, "this isn't real life!"
This isn't real life!
Are they leaving? They're just leaving the store?!
Your sandwich.
Hey, bud, welcome.
How are you, sir?
Everything he orders, just be like, "he's doing it! This guy's doing it!"
He's doing it. Six-inch club.
What kind of toppings would you like, sir?
Guys, ramp it up, ramp it up.
Sweet peppers.
Sweet peppers!
He's really making a sandwich now! Now we're making a sandwich!
What else would you like, sir?
Cucumbers, please.
Cucumbers!
He is so making this sandwich! He's making the sandwich!
A sandwich is being made!
What else?
He doesn't want to answer.
Oil and vinegar -- just a little bit.
Oil and vinegar! But just a little! Just a little.
Make it rain! Oil and vinegar, making it rain! Make it rain!
—Anything else?   —Yes.
I don't know if I can handle it!  I'm not sure!
Hit me -- what is it?
I want it toasted.
Toasted!
—Everything you knew about sandwiches is out the window!   —What the [bleep]
How do we toast it?
So, you boys went with the visors.
Q's looks like if he takes his visor off, he might be bald
then everything would come off at the same time, right?
What's up?
Let me get a regular-sized club.
Regular-sized club?
As you're making this guy's sandwich, just punch it.
Keep punching it -- bang!
What kind of bread?
Whole-wheat club.
Toppings?
Sal, just punch it right in the [bleep] middle.
Do you want any toppings on it?
Do you have black olives?
Destroy those black olives, Q.
Anything else?
Now, Sal, just drop a [bleep] elbow on it.
One hulk hoagie.
What's up, man?
—Sal looks stressed today, huh?  —Super-stress ball.
Q, give him, like a deep-tissue massage.
What type of bread would you like?
I thought you were just gonna -- I thought --
Sal wears the stress in his face, though.
Feels great. It feels great.
Q, bear hug him and start shaking him up and down.
How's that feel? Is that cracking your back?
It looks like he's assaulting him.
You want in on this, buddy?
"What's up, beef stick? What can I get you?"
How you doing, beef stick?
No. I would've taken the loss on that one, but you did it, so there you go.
You got it. Sal did it -- he called her beef stick. Q, now you call her beef stick.
The beef? You want the beef... Stick?
No, nice try.
Easy on the vinegar?
A lot of oregano.
A lot of oregano, right? That's how I like it, too. I'm the same way.
I can't do it. I can't do it.
You can do it, buddy, because other than that, we're gonna go down
and one of us is gonna face a loss at the end.
Yeah, but what does it even mean?
It doesn't mean much. That's why I want you to say it.
Would you like to make that a combo, beef stick?
Uh, yes.
It's that easy.
Do not let her walk out. I don't want to go down, dude.
You got it. No problem.
Right in half for...
He can't do it!
Have a great day, beef stick.
The window is closed.
Q and Sal couldn't "mustard" up a win
so they're first up on the loser board.
Today, we are teaming up to play a little game called "guess what you got to do."
Each team will have to perform an action
but only one member of the team will know what it is.
The teammate that knows the action
will have to give his partner hints to figure out what he has to do.
If you can't guess your task correctly and perform it, you lose, sucker pants!
They didn't do anything to you.
All right, I apologize. I came in hot.
Who's guessing? Who's giving the hints?
I will guess first.
Take your earpiece out, then.
Earpiece is out.
Murr, Sal has got to call somebody "pork chop."
Remember, you're only allowed to give one hint at a time.
I think I made the wrong choice with the food.
What did you get?
Yeah, chicken. I'm not a fan of chicken.
You know, don't get me wrong. I like white meat, just not chicken.
What the [bleep] is that supposed to mean?
That's not a hint.
That's a hint. That's a hint.
If that's a hint, I might as well just commit suicide.
I don't even know what to do.
Sal, that's all you get, buddy. Do something.
You like white meat, just not chicken.
Let me see -- is that very hot? Can I see that?
Oh, it is hot. It's hot. Thank you.
Nowhere near right.
Well, give me another hint, then.
Sorry interrupting you, man. I'm James, by the way.
What's your name?
Joseph
The nickname they call me is Murr. What do you they call you?
T-Zo
That's not a bad one, but doesn't really fit you well.
All right, Murr.
All right, this game's impossible.
What, do you want me to try on his chicken?
What the hell doesn't fit you well? Uh...
Oh, he's stuck on "fit you well."
Where did you get the hat?
'cause there's Lids right there. They have the store right there for the hats.
Oh, this is a disaster.
Is this a snapback hat?
Can I see?
I hope that was it.
No way near right.
Hey, do you know if there's any place that serves applesauce around here
or anything that goes with it?
Applesauce?
or anything that goes with it.
All right... Something that goes with applesauce -- pork chops.
Chops, pork, pork chop, pork...
What they call me is "Murr."
They call...
Oh, he's so close! He's so close!
Chops. Hey, pork chop.
He got it!
What's going on, pork chop?
We'll see you soon, pork chop.
Who's giving the clues and who's doing it?
I'll hint.
All right, I'll go. My earpiece is out.
All right, Q. He has got to... leapfrog over someone.
Oh, come on. That's impossible.
I mean, they're setting us up to fail.
Well, I mean, good luck.
I got some Chinese food
'cause I grew up next to -- my neighbors were chinese.
So I would go over, and his mother would cook us a big meal
And then we'd, you know... We'd do childhood games.
That's a hint.
You played childhood games when you were younger. That's interesting.
Chinese childhood games.
Duck...Duck...Duck... Goose!
That's not it?
We're talking about childhood games -- duck, duck, goose.
That's not it. Next clue.
You know what? There used to be a swamp here with lots of frogs in it.
Swamp ass?
I'm sorry, buddy. I just think I got to wipe your ass.
I think I just have to wipe your ass. I mean... Is that it?
That's not it.
That's not it...
He's up, he's up! It's over!
You had to leapfrog him, you idiot!
Oh, I focused on the "swamp," not the "frog."
Well, I'm just happy I didn't go for the wipe. I'm glad I asked him first.
Joe couldn't take the leap, so he and Q are splashing onto the loser board.
Today we're putting strangers through an unfortunate series of events.
While chatting someone up, the guys will give us an action to perform
Then another one, and then another one.
Here's the rub.
Every time you get a new action, you must redo the previous action first.
The goal is to remember and perform as many commands as you can.
Whoever performs the least loses.
And heads up, everybody. This is a joker versus joker challenge.
I'm so sorry. When you said that, a [bleep] bug smacked me in the face.
I slapped my nose, and it fell, and I looked around.
Let's do it.
This guy just threw up over the bench.
Every inch of the city is covered in piss and vomit. You know that, right?
Yep, I do. Actually, there's a report that said they [bleep] on everything.
Oh, so what do you think dirt is? It's dinosaur [bleep]?
Yeah. Dirt is -- all dirt is dinosaur [bleep].
I'm not sure if you're right on that one.
What are the oceans, then? Dinosaur piss?
No, it's water. What, are you ridiculous?
OK, Sal, ready, buddy?
—So you're just eating lunch?  —Yeah.
All right, Sal, you're gonna hit her with an ugly smile first.
Probably gonna get a sandwich myself.
There it is. Sal, you've got to squeeze both her shoulders.
But don't forget the first thing.
$3.
There it is.
That's the best. And I want to make sure I always go to the right place.
Who wants to go to a bad place? I want to go to the best place!
Sal, spin 360 degrees.
Look, if someone's gonna come up and they want a dollar
I can give a dollar at first.
But I only have so many, so I can't give it all day. You know I mean?
Give it all day? That's crazy.
What, am I made of money? I'm not made of money.
That would be insane!
Wow! He did it.
OK, Sal, ready, buddy? Do a pushup.
This is rough, man.
I'm here in the park.
Ugly smile. There you go.
I'm gonna enjoy it, the park.
This park is my park. But yours, too.
Yes, it's everyone's park.
I mean, I'll stay here all day. And you know what's better than this area?
Over there's better, and I like going over there by the fountain over there, too.
Uh, what was next?
I don't have time to exercise, so what am I gonna do?
I'll be walking to there... I just drop down...
He got it!
Lovely meeting you. Anna.
Anna, I'm Sal.
That was impressive, dude.
Oh, man.
High five, Sal. Well done.
—You a student?  —Yeah
Oh, cool, cool.
I'm gonna make the first one very difficult.
Q, say, "Hey, buckaroo. How are you?
Whipped cream on top and a cherry, too.
Wear pants and pleats? Yes, I do.
Steam engines go choo choo choo choo."
That's your first one.
Good luck remembering that [bleep].
Well, hey, buckaroo. How are you?
Cherry on top with whipped cream, too?
I wear pleated pants. How about you?
Steam engines go choo choo.
I don't know if I'm getting that right, but I like it.
Good. OK, the second thing
Take your shoe off and throw it across the park.
They're killing me.
All right, buddy, stick with me on this one.
OK, OK. Hey, buckaroo.
Uh...How are you?
Whipped cream on top and a cherry, too?
Where did -- wear pants with pleats?
Yes, I do.
The guy knows it better.
This is good. This is what I like about you.
Steam engines go choo choo choo!
OK. How do you like them shoes?
As in you want to wear them.
Well... Close. I kind of just want to throw them into that.
Are you gonna throw your shoes, also?
Yes, I'll let you throw mine.
All right, solidarity.
[bleep] let's do it.
Both of them or just one?
Just one, for now.
—I get to throw yours, also?  —Go ahead.
I love those boots.
Now fake box him to the stomach.
Oh, god.
Hey, buckaroo. How are you?
Whipped cream on top and a cherry, too?
Pants with pleats? Yes, I do.
A steam engine goes choo choo choo.
Can I borrow that other shoe?
Let's just see where this crazy train goes.
I'll give you mine.
What if you throw mine first?
This guy just wants to help.
Fake box.
High five, high five.
Stick with me, OK.
Ready? Here we go.
Hey, buckaroo. How are you?
Whipped cream on top and a cherry, too?
Pleated pants? Yes, I do.
A steam engine goes choo choo choo choo.
Out of shoes. I lose.
Q's out of shoes and out of luck, so it's time for his punishment.
So, Q is the big loser.
Yes, and tonight, he faces the mother of all punishments.
That's right, 'cause you're teaching Lamaze to a room full of pregnant women.
None of these kids are mine, right?
Every one!
Every one is mine? This is the worst punishment ever.
You're getting a kid! And you're getting a kid!
How far along is everybody? Far?
Is there any accidents here, or are they all planned?
What the [bleep] is he talking about?
OK. Breathing techniques. My name's Brian Quinn.
I'm a breathing expert, and I learned that in India.
You can't walk 2 feet in India without somebody grabbing you
and being like, "Hey, man, relax. Calm down, man."
This isn't Jamaica.
"Relaxing through labor. Demonstration." Wait, what?
Yeah, you're gonna demonstrate how to relax through labor, bud.
Oh, Stephanie.
This is your real punishment.
This device simulates the pains of childbirth.
So, what I'm gonna do, I'm gonna place the pads on your abdomen
And it's gonna contract your muscles just like during labor
Like a baby's about to come out.
There's eight levels of intensity.
Look at his face.
So, we're gonna put it on level 1, and it's as if your water just broke.
Tell them how to relax, buddy.
God. The key is to remain calm.
Don't tell somebody, "go [bleep] yourself"!
You got to relax through this.
I think we should give a minute... Dude...
So, that's like what contractions feel like, huh?
All right. So, now we're gonna go up to level 2, OK?
That was level 1! That was level 1.
[bleep] you guys. OK.
All right. I mean, it's bearable, obviously --
I can do it because I'm [bleep] doing it.
That little son of a bitch into the world
Clawing his way towards your genital -- right through your genitalia.
How do you girls do this?
What level is this?! What level is this?!
This is 8.
8?! This is 8?!
Oh, my god. Oh.
Aah. Oh, yeah!
Aah! Steph... You just...Cut the... [bleep] baby out.
Just get this stinking baby out of me!
Aah! Remember to breathe! Aah!
Ohh! Oh, my god! Oh, my god, I'm begging you.
Aah! OK, OK! What is  wrong with you?!
All right, that's it. You just had your baby.
So, now... Now starts the hard part -- what to name it.
Your punishment is now over, bud. Well done.